I-I call it pure evil.
So they've taken away his freedom of speech,
and now they've taken away his freedom of movement.
I mean, they had more allowances
for Khalid Sheikh Mohammed.
Oh, okay.
That sounds wild.
But I think Jesse Watters is a reasonable man,
because I was kicked in the head by a horse last week.
So...
let's hear him out.
How is Trump being treated
worse than the mastermind of 9-11?
A guy needs exercise. He's usually golfing.
And so you're gonna put a man who's almost 80
sitting in a room like this on his butt for all that time?
It's not healthy. He needs sunlight.
And he needs activity. He needs to be walking around.
He needs action.
It's really cruel and unusual puni...
punishment to make a man do that.
Are-are we talking about Donald Trump
or an old English sheepdog?
You can't keep him cooped up all day.
He needs time outside, or he'll pee on the couch.